This is kind of the last stop along the
way, draft process. You obviously were
on the field at the combine. How did you
think today compared? Yeah, it was cool.
Um definitely different, you know, being
in a familiar environment, throwing to,
you know, my guys that I've been
throwing to for the last, you know, year
and a half, 2 years. So, um it was cool
just to to get to play with those guys
one last time, you know, kind of get to
do our thing, have a little fun with it,
but it was awesome. What's something
that you
think that you can walk away saying that
you did it was great because we were out
there just having fun, you know, we've
been throwing routes on there in this
building for years. So,
um just doing our best at that and just
coming out here and just, you know,
showing who we are, you know, having a
little uh personality and uh having a
great time. How good is it to put the
injury behind you and show what you can
do?
>> Yeah, no, it was great. I mean, you
know, just again, wasn't out here trying
to prove anything, but you know, just
showing people, you know, when I when
I'm healthy, you know, when I'm myself,
you know, I think it's good enough. And
so, uh just trying to be me, trying to
be myself and have fun with it.
>> I don't know if you could see it, but
your dad was standing right behind you
and he was swaying back and forth the
whole entire time. Did he have some
nerves today? I'm sure he probably did.
He might lie and say he didn't, but uh I
would think as a daddy might have. So,
absolutely. How is that dynamic between
you two knowing he's just down the road
with the Saints?
>> Yeah, it's been really cool. I mean, he
was able to get to come to a couple of
my games this year. And so, it was it
was special for us, you know, um having
this last year with him so close and uh
being able to do things even in the off
season, you know, whether it's him
coming out to watch a baseball game or
whatever it was. It was so cool. And so,
um we're very grateful for this
opportunity. Yeah, how has this journey
compared to what you dreamed
up?
>> Yeah, it's been everything and more, you
know, it's been a grind, um but at the
same time, it's a dream come true. And
so, uh
I've been dreaming about this since I
was 4 years old. So, having this
opportunity is just it's a blessing. I'm
I'm super thankful. Your dad said
there's only one real 13 in the
household. He did let all of us know
that. You have any response? Uh no,
there there is one real 13, it's me. So,
my younger brother's the worst one,
that's what I like to call him, you
know, and he says that he's the real 13,
my dad's the OG, but I'm the fake. But,
we go back and forth on who the real 13
is all day. So, it's it's great. When
this is all said and done, draft day,
what are you hoping for? Um I'm just
somebody give me an opportunity, you
know, I'm I'm just looking for an
opportunity to to go prove that I belong
at the next level, you know, I've been
dreaming about this since I was a kid.
And so, um just looking for that chance.
And a lot of people are rooting for you.
So, thank you.
>> Appreciate it. Thank you. Absolutely.